Hayley Budzinski

Aurora, CO 80014

Phone: +1 (907) 350-4298

Email: hayleybudzinski@gmail.com

Objective and Summary

Experienced professional with a demonstrated history of working in a variety of administrative, clerical, and customer service-based positions. Through years working as a legal assistant, paralegal, and in the service industry, I have gained a wide variety of skills in written and verbal correspondence, organization, time management, and data tracking.

- Full Stacked Developer in Training
- 2+ years in legal
- 6+ years in customer service
- 4+ years in retail
- 3+ years in food and beverage
- Colorado Notary Public
- Work experience in five countries

Web Development Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- iQuery
- Web API's, Third-Party API's, Server-Side API's

Work Experience

Hoffman Nies Dave & Meyer, LLP October 2019 – Present Paralegal

- Independently correspond with and maintain client relationships
- Draft, review, and revise Estate Planning Documents
- Assist in the formation of Nonprofits and LLCs
- Maintain attorney schedules and coordinate client meetings
- Working knowledge of the Colorado Court E-Filing Systems and Secretary of State Filings
- Daily use of Outlook, Microsoft Word and Excel, Tabs Billing System, Adobe Acrobat

White Bear Ankele Tanaka & Waldron, March 2017 – September 2019 Paralegal

- Research and data collection and tracking using Practice Master and other data tracking tools for over 130 Metropolitan Districts around Colorado
- Independently correspond with and maintain client relationships
- Draft, review, and revise contracts and agreements
- Maintain annual compliance matters and statutory deadlines
- Maintain attorney schedules and coordinate client meetings
- Correspond with and assist multiple attorneys and governmental entities
- Daily correspondence with and working knowledge of the Colorado Court Filing Systems
- Daily use of Outlook, Microsoft Word and Excel, Practice Master, Tabs Billing System, Adobe Acrobat

Bunsen, Dublin, Ireland, November 2015 - September 2016 Supervisor

- Ensure open communication among staff and customers
- Organize and operate multiple restaurant management systems
- Handling guest and employee complaints and comments
- Comply with financial transaction policies
- Ensure up-to-date tracking of all transactions including employee hours and distribution of tips
- Play integral part in opening new restaurant branch

Ak Starfish Co., Anchorage, Alaska 2010-2012

- Sales Associate
- Assist in opening secondary location of shop

Education

Colorado State University, Fort Collins, Colorado

Earned: Bachelor of Arts Degree in International Studies and International Development

Graduation date: May 17, 2014